BRIAN DOAN

8417 Stark Dr., Indianapolis, Indiana 46216 | (317) 495-8720 | briandoan71@yahoo.com | LinkedIn

Summary

Three years of professional experience in IT and customer service in hardware/software troubleshooting and hospitality, utilizing skills to collaborate with clients and the business to quickly find solutions to problems. Alum of the Salesforce and Deloitte Pathfinder program looking for a junior level admin role with enthusiasm to help and learn from a team through the Salesforce platform. Passion to be a part of a team that does their best to help those around them succeed.

Skills & Highlights

- Certified Salesforce Administrator
- Certified CompTIA A+ IT Professional
- Certified TestOut PC Pro
- Bilingual in English and Vietnamese

- Beginner knowledge of HTML, CSS
- Beginner knowledge of Agile methodologies
- Eager problem-solver

Professional Experience

Chick-Fil-A (Indianapolis, IN)

Aug 2019 - May 2020

Team Member

- Built a rapport with customers to provide a unique experience to capture new long term customers
- Provided technical support for the business equipment and management tools to lessen downtime and stress of team members
- Served 50-100 customers within the lunch rush hours to meet store hourly net profit goals

Fry's Electronics (Fishers, IN)

Nov 2017 - Oct 2019

Computer Sales Associate

- Maintained a working knowledge of current technologies to inform customers to generate store sales
- Worked with POS machines to create discount tags for merchandise markdowns to lessen tasks for management staff and quickly service customers
- Merchandised 20 products weekly using UPC codes to provide customers with new products offering available guickly

Sunnyside Road Baptist Church (Indianapolis, IN)

Feb 2017 - Dec 2018

WordPress/IT Specialist

- Maintained and updated old hardware for the staff and equipment for easier usability among nontechnical staff
- Rebuilt entire web presence with a website and reengaging social media interaction
- Built presentations using MediaShout software to provide smooth transitions within the services
- Implemented availability of recordings of sermons online to provide more traffic to website

Education

Salesforce and Deloitte Pathfinder Program (Indianapolis, IN)

Mar 2020 - June 2020

Administrator Certification

- Salesforce and Deloitte joint program to build Salesforce Administrator and business soft skills which provides 100+ hours of Salesforce technical training
- Certified Salesforce Admin and Completed 49 Badges and 1 Super Badge, achieved Trailhead Mountaineer rank
- Advanced technical training skills include: Data management (incl. data modeling, security and data access), automation using workflow rules and process builder and reports / dashboards

Eleven Fifty Academy (Fishers, IN)

Jun 2019 - Aug 2019

JavaScript Accelerated Learning Program

- Learned the basics of HTML and CSS to build out simple frontend websites
- Applied JavaScript knowledge using its libraries and frameworks such as Angular, React, Node, and Express to build more intermediate frontend and backend of websites that are deployed
- Built RESTful APIs through PostgreSQL

IUPUI (Indianapolis, IN)

Aug 2016 - May 2017

Music Technology

- Relevant coursework: Introduction to IT (internet safety: ransomware, phishing, etc.)
- Other coursework: Auditory Music Listening, Piano, Vocal primary for major